Guide to the Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Education Serials TAM.767
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Education Serials
1883-2016
1940-1989
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
TAM.767
6 Linear Feet in 12 manuscript boxes and 5 flat boxes
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Education Serials contains over 200 titles on education in the United States (US) and other countries. The collection dates between 1883 and 2016, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1940s through the 1980s. Topics include elementary, high school, and college level education and curricula; student organizations; cultural institutions; and professional organizations related to education.
Arrangement
Serials in this collection are arranged alphabetically by title.
Conditions Governing Access
Open to users without restriction.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
This collection combines serials relating to education drawn from two discrete groups of material held by the Tamiment Library. The first was a partially inventoried backlog of serials, received by the library through donations, subscriptions, and in archival collections. The second group consisted of around 1,700 serials, newspapers, and magazines, organized by title as an artificial collection, referred to as Periodicals.001 or Boxed Newspapers. This material was combined, inventoried, and arranged and described in subject-based categories in 2017. The accession number related to this collection is 2017.049.
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Due to the fragile nature of certain original materials, researchers may be required to consult microfilm copies, preservation photocopies, or digital images of material in this collection.
Scope and Contents
The Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives Collection of Education Serials contains over 200 titles on education in the United States (US) and other countries. The collection dates between 1883 and 2016, with the bulk of the material dating from the 1940s through the 1980s. Topics include elementary, high school, and college level education and curricula; student organizations; cultural institutions; and professional organizations related to education. The bulk of the serials in the collection were published in the US, with other titles from Europe, Latin America, Canada, Africa, and Asia. There are a number of serials published by the New University Conference in Chicago, Illinois in the early 1970s; by Iranian student organizations in the US and the United Kingdom in the 1970s and 1980s; and by the Ministry of Education in Cuba from the 1960s through the 1990s.
Education -- United States.; Serials (publications); Teaching -- United States; Students -- Political activity.; New University Conference (U.S.)
- Advocate: Advocates for Children of New York, Inc., Long Island City, NY, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Advocate: Community College Association, Burlingame, CA, 2000 (Box 12, Folder 1)
- Al-Basit: Revista de Estudios Albacetenses, Spain, 1996 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Alumni for a New Columbia: Alumni for a New Columbia, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Alumni UpDate: Alumni & Friends of LaGuardia High School, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 4, Box 15, Folder 1)
- American Capitalism: Council for Advancement of Secondary Education, Washington, DC, 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- American Studies International Newsletter: American Studies International at George Washington University, Washington, DC, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Annasach: University of Dundee, Dundee, Scotland, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
- Annual Report: International Institute of Social History, Amsterdam, Netherlands, 1994-2005 (Box 1, Folder 7-8)
- APHA Newsletter: American Printing History Association, Brooklyn, NY, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 2)
- Arma Nueva: La Comision Nacional de Alfabetizacion del Ministerio de Educacion, Havana, Cuba, 1960 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- ARSE: Architectural Radicals, Students & Educators Group, London, UK, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Art Student News: Young American Artists Association, New York, NY, 1941 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- ASA: Asian Students Association Magazine: Asian Students Association, Kowloon, Hong Kong, 1996-1997 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- At Issue: Barnard Strike Committee, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Attica Brigade: Attica Brigade, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 12, Folder 4, Box 14, Folder 1)
- Baltimore School: A Learning Network: Baltimore School, Baltimore, MD, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
- Beacon: South Street Seaport Museum, New York, NY, 1995 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Better Schools: National Citizens Commission for Public Schools, New York, NY, 1955 (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Black Rap: Black Students for Black Action at Lake Forest College, Lake Forest, IL, 1970-1973 (Box 13, Folder 1-2)
- Bread & Butter: Consumers Union of the United States, Inc., New York, NY, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Breakthrough: A Publication of Global Education Associates: Global Education Associates, East Orange, NJ, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Brief History of the United States: Chinese Translation Group, Emeryville, CA, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Brotherhood News: Free Press of Louisville, Louisville, KY, Undated (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Bulletin du Syndicat National de l'Enseignement Superieur: National de l'Enseignement Superieur, Paris, France, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bulletin of the Wage-Earners' Institute: The Thomas Davidson Society, New York, NY, 1917-1918 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Campus Rebels: The Pacific Publishing Foundation, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 1, Folder 20)
- CCRP Record: Cornell Corporate Responsibility Project Record, Ithaca, NY, 1977 (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Center Report: Center for the Study of Democratic Institutions, Santa Barbara, CA, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Chicago Maroon: Chicago Maroon, Chicago, IL, 1968 (Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 9)
- Chutzpah: Chutzpah Collective, Chicago, IL, 1973-1974 (Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 5-6, Box 15, Folder 3)
- Civic Leader: Civic Education Service, Washington, DC, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Closed Classroom: The Raritan Caucus Press, Piscatawdy, NJ, 1974 (Box 16, Folder 5)
- CLR Reports: Council on Library Resources, Washington, DC, 1992 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Co-operative Education: Inter-Co-Operative Committee, Brooklyn, NY, 1920 (Box 12, Folder 6)
- Collector, The: Walter R. Benjamin Autographs, New York, NY, 1958 (Box 15, Folder 4)
- College News: National Student League of Greater New York, New York, NY, 1933 (Box 13, Folder 4)
- College Voice: National Student League of Greater New York, New York, NY, 1933 (Box 11, Folder 2)
- Compass: Compass Review, New York, NY, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Computer Use in Social Services Network: University of Texas at Arlington, Arlington, TX, 1989-1991 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Confederation of Iranian Students Report: Confederation of Iranian Students, Berkeley, CA, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Counter-Attack: Committee Against Academic Repression, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 3)
- Counter Attack; New Haven Panther Defense Committee, New Haven, CT, circa 1970s (Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 7)
- Crisis in the Schools: Teachers & the Community: Independent Socialist Clubs of America, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Critical Mass: Department of Sociology, University of Tennessee-Knoxville, Knoxville, TN, 1975 (Box 15, Folder 5)
- Crosscurrents: The Institute for Global Studies in Culture, Power & History, Johns Hopkins University, Baltimore, MD, 1994-1996 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Csula Mecha: Cal State Los Angeles MECHA, Los Angeles, CA, 1973 (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Daily Index on Education: National Education Association: Office of Government Relations and Citizenship, Washington, DC, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Daycare Newsletter: Daycare Committee to Fight Budget Cuts, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- De Facto: Student Group for Political Analysis, Minneapolis, MN, 1950 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- DE: IUS Magazine on the Democratization and Reform of Education: Czechslovakia, 1990 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Democracy's Defense Through Education: Defense Bulletin: National Commission for the Defense of Democracy Through Education, Washington, DC, 1948-1950 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Discursos en Ciudad Libertad: Ministerio de Educacion / Editorial Hercules, Cuba, Undated (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Disorientation: UC Berkeley, Berkeley, CA, 1977 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Disorientation 2000: University of Wisconsin-Madison, Madison, WI, 1967 (Box 15, Folder 6)
- Down the Up Staircase: New University Conference, Chicago, IL, 1971 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Economics: Totalitarian Domination of the Quantitative: Council for Conscious Existence, Cambridge, MA, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Educacion: Ministerio de Educacion, Havana, Cuba, 1967-1991 (Box 2, Folder 10-13, Box 3, Folder 1-5)
- Educate Agitate Organize: Education Workers Industrial Union 620, Cambridge, MA, Undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Education Digest: Prakken Publications, Inc., Ann Arbor, MI, 1987 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Educational Signpost: American Education Association, Brooklyn, NY, 1940 (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Elimu: Department of Black Studies at University of California at Santa Barbara, Santa Barbara, CA, 1990-1991 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Equal Professor: Equal Commission NYU, New York, NY, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- ETC.: A Review of General Semantics: International Society for General Semantics, San Francisco, CA, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 9)
- European Studies Forum: Council for European Studies, New York, NY, 2007 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Evacuation Day: James Riker, New York, NY, 1883 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Faculty Action: Faculty Action, New York, NY, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 8)
- FAS: Public Interest Report: Journal of the Federation of American Scientists, Washington, DC, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- FBLA Forum: Future Business Leaders of America, Washington, DC, 1954 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Federal Union World: Federal Union, Inc, Washington, DC, 1943 (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Free Campus News: Young Americans for Freedom, Washington, DC, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Free Critic: City College San Francisco, San Francisco, CA, 1972 (Box 14, Folder 3, Box Shared Tamiment 053, Folder 8)
- Free You: Midpeninsula Free University, Menlo Park, CA, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 14, Box 11, Folder 4)
- Global Vistas: Center for International Studies, Bergen Community College, Paramus, NJ, 1989 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Gradside: Graduate Student Association of the University of Rhode Island, Providence, RI, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Great Brain Robbery: Moss Side Press Ltd., Manchester, UK, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3, Box 15, Folder 7)
- Green and Gold: Eli Whitney Vocational High School, Brooklyn, NY, 1971 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Harbus News: Harbus News, Cambridge, MA, 1946 (Box 11, Folder 5)
- Heritage: Southern California Library for Social Studies and Research, Los Angeles, CA, 1990-1991 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- High Points: Board of Education, City of New York, New York, NY, 1937 (Box 15, Folder 8)
- Historic New Orleans Collection Quarterly: Kemper and Leila Williams Foundation, New Orleans, LA, 1984-1995 (Box 4, Folder 7-8)
- History of Science Society Newsletter: History of Science Society, Worcester, MA, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 9)
- Human Affairs: Pine Tree Publications, Ontario, Canada, 1983 (Box 15, Folder 10)
- Humanities News: New York Council for the Humanities, New York, NY, 1979-1990 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Idaho Yesterdays: Idaho Historical Society, Boise, ID, 1960 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Impact: PACT, New York, NY, 1967 (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Impact!: The Boston Computer Society Social Impact Group & Public Service Committee, Cambridge, MA, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Informer: Boston University Student Congress, Boston, MA, 1968 (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Intercollegiate Society of Individualists: Intercollegiate Society of Individualists, Philadelphia, PA, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
- International Council for Adult Education: The International Council for Adult Education, Toronto, Ontario, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
- International Gramsci Society Newsletter: English Department of the University of Notre Dame, Notre Dame, IN, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- International Update: Nature Conservancy, Arlington, VA, 1990-1993 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Iran in Resistance: Iranian Student Association Throughout the US, Austin, TX, 1983-1987 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Iran News & Review: Iranian Students Association in SC, Los Angeles, CA, 1979 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Iranian Students Association: Iranian Students Association in the United States, College Park, MD, Undated (Box 4, Folder 18)
- IRRA Newsletter: Industrial Relations Research Association, Madison, WI, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 19)
- ISA Review: Iranian Student Association, Berkeley, CA, 1978 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Issues in Education and Culture: Institute for the Humanities, Simon Fraser University, Burnaby, British Columbia, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Journal of Unconventional History: Journal of Unconventional History, Cardiff-by-the-Sea, CA, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Knowledge-Index News: Dialog Information Services, Inc., Palo Alto, CA, 1990 (Box 16, Folder 1)
- La Botella Universitaria: La Asociacion de Intercambio Cultural Universitario, Madrid, Spain, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- La Gente: Associated Students of UCLA, Los Angeles, CA, 1971 (Box 14, Folder 4)
- LAMAS Newsletter: London and Middlesex Archaeological Society, London, UK, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Leadership News: American Association of School Administrators, Arlington, VA, 1991 (Box 11, Folder 6)
- Learning Bini / English: Language Press, Benin City, Nigeria, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Legislative Conference News / Published by the Legislative Conference of the City University of New York: Legislative Conference of CUNY, New York, NY, 1964-1968 (Box 11, Folder 7)
- Les Cahiers d'Encrages: Les Cahiers d'Encrages, Paris, France, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Let's Read: Jamal Foundation, Kingston, NY, 1977 (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Liberty: Students for a Libertarian Society, San Francisco, CA, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
- Liberty Log: Liberty Ship Project: National Maritime Historical Society, Brooklyn, NY, 1979-1984 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- LIFEline: Leadership Institute for Educators, Brooklyn, NY, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Lightning: Lightning, Storrs, CT, 1971-1972 (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Linen & Trace: Frederick Law Olmstead National Historic Site, Brookline, MA, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Link: Woochefee Bulletin for Cultural Cooperation, New York, NY, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- Living Historian: The Living History Association, Inc., Wilmington, VT, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Looking Left: Looking Left, Binghamton, NY, 1974 (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Manas: Manas Publishing Company, Los Angeles, CA, 1948 (Box 16, Folder 2)
- Materiaux pour l'Histoire de Notre Temps: Bibliotheque de Documentation Internationale Contemporaine, Paris, France, 1990-2000 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Merrill Mirror: Merrill Junior High, Oshkosh, WI, 1949 (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Midcontinent American Studies Journal: Midcontinent American Studies Association/University of Kansas, Lawrence, KS, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Mitteilungen aus der Kulturwissenschaftlichen Forschung: Lehrstuhl Kulturtheorie der Sektion Ästhetik und Kunstwissenschaften der Humboldt-Universität zu Berlin, Berlin, Germany, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Mojo: Mojo, New York, NY, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 8)
- Monteith Journal: The Monteith Journal, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- National Bulletin: Co-operative Commonwealth University Federation, Ontario, 1954 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- NCBE Forum: The George Washington University & the Center for Applied Linguistics, Washington, DC, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 15)
- NCPH Public History News: National Council on Public History / Department of History and POLIS, Indiana University, Indianapolis, IN, 1991-1996 (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Net News: Institute for Global Communications, San Francisco, CA, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Network: Community Memory Project, Berkeley, CA, 1991 (Box 5, Folder 18)
- New Dimensions: The Balch Institute for Ethnic Studies, Philadelphia, PA, 1987-1992 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- New England Public Alternative Schools: New England Public Alternative Schools, Hartford, CT, Undated (Box 5, Folder 20)
- New Faculty News: The Church Society for College Work, Cambridge, MA, 1972 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- New Management: University of Southern California, Graduate School of Business Administration, Costa Mesa, CA, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- New Standards: J.P. Bedford, London, UK, 1923 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- New Union Voices: Hofstra University Institute of Applied Social Science, Hempstead, NY, 1980 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- New University Newsletter: New University Newsletter, Madison, WI, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- New York High School Free Press: NY High School Free Press, New York, NY, 1968 (Box 14, Folder 5)
- News of Southern Summer School for Women Workers in Industry: Southern Summer School for Women Workers in Industry, Baltimore, MD, 1931 (Box 11, Folder 9)
- Newsletter: College Democrats of America, Washington, DC, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Newsletter: Committee for Academic Freedom in Africa, Portland, ME, 1993 (Box 5, Folder 27-28)
- Newsletter: Documentary Heritage Program, Cheektowaga, NY, 1996-1997 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Newsletter: Welsh-American Genealogical Society (WAGS), Poultney, VT, 1995 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- NJEA Review: NJ Education Association, Trenton, NJ, 1990 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- No More Teachers Dirty Looks: Bay Area Radical Teachers Organ Committee, San Francisco, CA, 1970-1975 (Box 6, Folder 2, Box 11, Folder 10)
- NSIC Newsletter: National Strike Information Center, Waltham, MA, 1970 (Box 13, Folder 10)
- NUC Newsletter: New University Conference, Chicago, IL, 1970-1971 (Box 6, Folder 3-5, Box 7, Folder 1-2, Box 11, Folder 11, Box 14, Folder 6)
- NUC Papers: New University Conference, Chicago, IL, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 3)
- NUC Region 2 Newsletter: New University Conference, Chicago, IL, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 4)
- NUC Women's Caucus Newsletter: New University Conference, Chicago, IL, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
- NUC-MLC Newsletter: New University Conference, Madison, WI, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 12)
- NYU Local News: NYU, New York, NY, 1971 (Box 7, Folder 7, Box 11, Folder 13)
- NYU Local Newsletter: NYU, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 8)
- NYU Local: Library Newsletter: NYU, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- NYU Staff Focus: New York University, New York, NY, 1996 (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Objectively: National Education Association, Washington, DC, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 10)
- OHMAR Newsletter: Oral History in the Mid-Atlantic Region, Washington, DC, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Old Greenwich: Half Moon Series, New York, NY, Undated (Box 7, Folder 12)
- On Campus: American Federation of Teachers, Washington, DC, 1989-1996 (Box 14, Folder 7-11)
- Open Admissions Newsletter: Attica Brigade, New York, NY, Undated (Box 12, Folder 14, Box 14, Folder 12)
- Palimpsest: Office of the State Historical Society, Iowa City, IA, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 15)
- Pangolin: Pangolin Corporation, New York, NY, 1970 (Box 12, Folder 15)
- PARE Paper: People Against Racism in Education, New York, NY, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Partisan: Le Mouvement Revolutionnaire des Etudiants du Quebec, Montreal, Quebec, 1974 (Box 7, Folder 17, Box 12, Folder 16-17)
- Pedagogo: Colegio de Pedagogos en el Exilio y de la Federacion de Educadores Cubanos Democraticos, Miami, FL, 1969 (Box 7, Folder 18)
- People for the American Way News: People for the American Way, Washington, DC, 1996-1997 (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Pine Torch: Piney Woods Country Life School, Piney Woods, MS, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 13)
- Polina-Amerykanski: Polinia Alamanac, Detroit, MI, 1944 (Box 16, Folder 3-4)
- Political Economy of Youth: Radical Education Project, New York, NY, Undated (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Positive Outcome of Philosophy: Charles H. Kerr and Co., Chicago, IL, 1906 (Box 8, Folder 1)
- Preservation Action Alert: Preservation Action in Washington DC, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 2)
- Preservation League of New York State Newslettter: The Preservation League of New York State, Albany, NY, 1985-1995 (Box 8, Folder 3)
- President's Report: School Administrators and Supervisors Organizing Committee, New York, NY, 1974-1976 (Box 8, Folder 4)
- Probe: Probe, Boston, MA, 1945-1946 (Box 8, Folder 5)
- Progressive Librarian: Progressive Librarians Guild, New York, NY, 1997-1999 (Box 8, Folder 6)
- Progressive Student: Progressive Student Network, Iowa City, IA, 1987-1989 (Box 12, Folder 19, Box 13, Folder 11)
- Psicologia y Educacion: Ministerio de Educacion, Havana, Cuba, 1964-1968 (Box 6, Folder 6-7, Box 7, Folder 13)
- Public Alternative Schools: National Alternative Schools Program, Amherst, MA, 1973 (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Public and the Schools: Public Education Association, New York, NY, 1943 (Box 8, Folder 7)
- Rampart Journal of Individualist Thought: Rampart College, Boulder, CO, 1965 (Box 8, Folder 8)
- Rapport: Universite Libre de Bruxelles, Brussels, Belgium, 1893 (Box 8, Folder 9)
- Ready or Not: Amalgamated Bank of New York, New York, NY, 1981 (Box 16, Folder 6)
- Red Pencil: Boston Area Teaching Project, Inc., Boston, MA, 1972 (Box 11, Folder 14, Box 12, Folder 20)
- Reporter: Science, Technology, and Society, University Park, PA, 1985 (Box 8, Folder 10)
- Rethinking Schools: Rethinking Schools, Milwaukee, WI, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Revista Referativa de Educacion: Centro Nacional de Documentación e Información Pedagógicas, Havana, Cuba, 1982 (Box 8, Folder 11)
- Rote Presse Korrespondenz: Rote Presse Korrespondenz, Berlin, Germany, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 12)
- Round One: Development Education Resources Service, Halifax, Nova Scotia, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 13)
- Salad Bowl: American Studies Association of Rutgers, New Brunswick, NJ, 2002 (Box 8, Folder 14)
- Sansculottes: Free Youth Press, New York, NY, Undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Save NYA Aid: American Youth Congress Coalition, New York, NY, 1940 (Box 9, Folder 1)
- SAWSJ Links: SAWSJ, Amherst, MA, 1997 (Box 9, Folder 2)
- School and Society: Columbia University Press, New York, NY, 1937 (Box 9, Folder 3)
- School and Society: Science Press, Lancaster, PA, 1927 (Box 9, Folder 4)
- School Nurse: NEA Department of School Nurses, Washington, DC, 1972 (Box 9, Folder 5)
- School Voices: School Voices, New York, NY, 1991-1993 (Box 12, Folder 23)
- Secretariat Reports: International Union of Students, Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 6)
- Situaciones: Universitania Veracruzana, Mexico, 1960 (Box 16, Folder 9)
- Skeptic: Skeptic Magazine, Inc., Santa Barbara, CA, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 7)
- Slingshot: ASUC sponsored, Berkeley, CA, 1989-2016 (Box 9, Folder 8, Box 14, Folder 14)
- SLS: Students for a Libertarian Society: Students for a Libertarian Society, San Francisco, CA, 1977-1979 (Box 9, Folder 9)
- Something Else!: Radical Education Project, Ann Arbor, MI, 1969 (Box 9, Folder 10)
- Speakout!: Columbia University Workers, New York, NY, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 11)
- Spectrum: Immigration History Research Center, St. Paul, MN, 1976 (Box 9, Folder 12, Box 16, Folder 7)
- Sport: International Union of Students, Prague, Czechoslovakia, 1973 (Box 9, Folder 13)
- SRRT Newsletter: Social Responsibilities Round Table of the American Library Association, Chicago, IL, 1996 (Box 9, Folder 14)
- Staff Bulletin: Board of Education, Brooklyn, NY, 1962-1964 (Box 9, Folder 15)
- Startle!: Greater New Haven High School Free Press, Guilford, CT, 1970 (Box 9, Folder 16)
- Strike Daily One / Strike Daily Two: Old Mole, Cambridge, MA, 1969 (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Strike!: Northeastern Federation of Anarcho-Communists (NEFAC), New York, NY, 2004 (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Student Action: National Student Action Center, Washington, DC, 1987 (Box 9, Folder 17)